Ivanchuk Ivan, Java Middle developer

(+7) 988-061-84-72 | l3r8y@duck.com | t.me.l3r8y | blog | github.com/l3r8yJ | linkedin

Experience

VTB | Java Middle Developer | 03.04.2023 - present.

• Integration of banking systems. Work on CRM for the banking segment.

Java 11, Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL, Liquibase

Open Source | Java developer | 24.06.2022 - present.

• R&D development. Worked on code quality control tools, eolang programming language, maven plugins Java, Maven, XSL, Docker, Unit Testing, Integration Testing, Rust, Ruby, EO, LATEX

INTERVOLGA | 19.04.2022 - 04.08.2022

• B2B development. Worked on integration of 1c-bitrix PHP, 1c-bitrix framework, SQL

Freelance | Java developer | May 2021 - April 2022

• Development of telegram bots for trading cryptocurrency platform Java, TelegramBots, Spring, SpringBoot, SpringData, Docker

Skills

- Java | Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Gradle, Liquibase
- RDBMS | PostgreSQL
- CI/CD | Openshift, K8s, TeamCity, Docker, GitHub Actions, rultor, 0pdd
- VCS | Git, GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket
- Other | Ruby, Rust, Kotlin

Languages

English | B1 intermediate

Russian | C1 native

Education

Volgograd State Technical University |

Bachelor, Engineering and Economics, Software engineering

2020 - 2024

Courses and etc.

Completely self-taught by reading books and practicing a lot.

I also have a small blog about software, perhaps it will be of interest to you. [link]

About

Currently involved in open source development. Main organizations that i contribute:

- EO.
- EO-CQRS.

I also have my own open source projects, one of them is a Ruby library. It has reached 6,000 downloads.

I am highly interested in the development of R&D. I have experience in conducting research and publishing scientific papers. I also have experience in developing programming language, maven plugins, static analysis and quality control tools. I also have experience in teaching students in the discipline "Theory of Formal Languages".